PAGE   003  ECBRAM  .SA:1 TXRRAM RAM off the direct page.

00816                             XDEF   USRTAB
00817            0034    D USRTAB EQU    STUB0+&2*STBLEN 20 bytes are needed for the USR
00818                      •    address table (USRTAB).  There is
00819                      *    no place else to put USRTAB in the
00820                      *    extended version so it overlays
00821                      *    stubs 2 and 3.  This is OK since only
00822                      *    stub 0 is in use, with stub 1
00823                      *    acting as the stopper.  However, in
00824                      *    the disk version (or any version using
00825                      *    stub 1 or higher), it will be
00826                      *    necessary to allocate more memory for
00827                      *    temporary storage and move USRTAB into
00828                      *    the new area. For this reason, USRTAB
00829                      *    is referenced indirectly through the
00830                      *    direct page location USTBAD.
